thatssotrue.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy - Gif Stories - That's So True

Your privacy is important to Spartz Inc. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information Spartz Inc collects, and the ways in which Spartz Inc uses that personal information. 

### Personal information collection

The types of personal information Spartz Inc collects are: 

  * Information about your use of this website
  * Information that you provide for the purposes of registering for this website
  * Information about transactions carried out over this website
  * Information you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services
  * Demographic and interests reporting
  * Any other information that you send Spartz Inc

### Using Personal Information

Spartz Inc may use your personal information to: 

  * Administer this website
  * Personalize this website for you
  * Enable your access to and use of the website services
  * Publish information about you on the website
  * Send you products that you purchase
  * Send you statements and invoices
  * Collect payments from you and
  * Send you marketing communications

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. Where Spartz Inc discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors, for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement. In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Spartz Inc may disclose your personal information to the extent that is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights. 

### Securing your Data

Spartz Inc will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Spartz Inc will store all the information you provide (on its secure servers). [Information relating to electronic transfers entered into via this website will be protected via encrypted technology.] 

### Cross-border Data Transfers

Information that Spartz Inc collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which Spartz Inc operates to enable the use of information in accordance with this privacy policy. [In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on this website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.] You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information. 

### Using Cookies

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn or more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising for some companies, you can visit http://http://www.networkadvertising.org and http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp 

### Consent

By using our site, you consent to our website's privacy policy. 

### Updating this Statement

Spartz Inc may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. You should check the page periodically to ensure you are familiar with any changes. 

### Other Websites

This website contains links to other websites. Spartz Inc is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party. 

### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We do not provide services directed to children or otherwise target our site to children, and we do not collect personal information from children under the age of 13. No content that depicts, describes, identifies or otherwise relates to an individual under the age of 13 may be submitted to us, and no such content or other information relating to an individual under the age of 13 will be knowingly solicited or received by us. 

### Contact

If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or if you wish to change or delete any information previously provided by you or collected from you, you may contact us at: [info@spartzinc.com](mailto:info@spartzinc.com) or by calling 312.880.7207.
